usenetbinaries.com 2014-06-30

# UsenetBinaries.com - Privacy Policy

**UsenetBinaries.com Privacy Statement**

This privacy statement covers the site www.usenetbinaries.com and all other sites in the UsenetBinaries.com domain name space, such as admin.usenetbinaries.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users� privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices. 

  1. What personally identifiable information UsenetBinaries.com collects. 
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.  

  3. What organization collects the information.  

  4. How UsenetBinaries.com uses the information.  

  5. With whom UsenetBinaries.com may share user information.  

  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.  

  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under UsenetBinaries.com control.   

  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.   

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact UsenetBinaries.com through http://www.usenetbinaries.com/contact. 

#### Information Collection

UsenetBinaries.com is the sole owner of the information collected on UsenetBinaries.com. UsenetBinaries.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

_Registration_

In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to provide contact information and unique identifiers (such as username, password, and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest and to authenticate access to registered user site features. 

_Upgrade_

We request information from the user on our upgrade form. A user must provide contact information (such as billing address and phone number) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer�s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the user will be contacted via email address or billing information as necessary. 

#### Information Use

UsenetBinaries.com uses information about our users for registration, billing, authentication, site features, customer communications, and site security. Site features include the downloading of images and videos, uploading of images, and searching for site media. 

#### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, database records, and log files. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users, which details their **optional** viewing preferences (e.g. �Group Favorites�). If a user does not explicitly store viewing preferences, none are collected or stored. Consequently, this optional information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user�s visit to our Web site. We do not share your profile with other third parties. Your profile is stored with your username and password, but not with any personally identifiable data from your billing information. Also, we do not reveal personal viewing preferences in any customer support tools. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user�s computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user�s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. the user will not be able to use registered user features such as viewing full media or performing searches. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the Profile�section. 

Cookies contain information collected at signup time, including IP address, referrer, and username. 

#### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files.� This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information which is used only in matters of site abuse and security. We use a log analyzing utility which uses log files to analyze user movement in the aggregate. 

#### Communications from the Site

_Special Offers and Updates_

We send all new members a validation email containing a hyperlink which validates their email address in order to complete registration on our site. Free members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Paid users do not receive these emails. 

_Service Announcements_

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. 

_Customer Service_

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email and our web-based contact form. 

#### Sharing

_Legal Disclaimer_

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

**We do not share personal information with third parties with the following exceptions.**

_Third Party Intermediaries_

We use credit card processing companies to authenticate and bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We may also use a third party intermediary to assist us in analyzing broad demographic information about our site traffic. 

_Business Transitions_

In the event UsenetBinaries.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users� personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

_Site Security and Abuse_

In the event an attempt is made by any user to disrupt our service, circumvent our Terms of Service, or otherwise engage in activity which causes us concern regarding the normal operation of our service or site security, we reserve the right to share personal information with ISP administrators in order to resolve the issue and/or personally identify the user for further action. 

#### Choice/Opt-out

Since all personal information is not optionally shared with third parties, there is no opt-out of information use at UsenetBinaries.com. Promotional emails are a mandatory condition of free accounts. 

#### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, UsenetBinaries.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

####  Surveys and Contests

From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Anonymous Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users� personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users� personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

#### Email to a Friend

If a user elects to use our Email To a Friend service for sending images to a friend, we ask them for the friend�s email address. UsenetBinaries.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site containing the selected media and associated images. UsenetBinaries.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

#### Upload Form

UsenetBinaries.com allows users to upload files to the Usenet network, which will then be distributed worldwide according to the operation of the Usenet global system. The post will include the user's email address they used to sign up with UsenetBinaries.com. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, Usenet, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

#### Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users�information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our upgrade form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just surfing. In some cases, an upgrade form may not display the lock as the form is not displayed on a secure page. However, anything typed into that form will be submitted encrypted, and any re-display of the form with the information enclosed (for, example, data correction purposes) will be sent over SSL. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users�information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. When new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users� information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage in a locked facility. 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can contact us via http://www.usenetbinaries.com/contact. 

#### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If a user�s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct or update users� personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at https://admin.usenetbinaries.com/cgi-bin/admin or by emailing our Customer Support at http://www.usenetbinaries.com/contact 

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users�personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

#### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at http://www.usenetbinaries.com/contact.
